Welcome to our training "Manage Your Experiments - Interpret Results for Listing Content You've
Tested."
In this third video of the "Manage Your Experiments" series, we'll show you how to view, assess,
and apply the results of an M-Y-E Test.
If you haven't watched our earlier videos on planning and setting up an M-Y-E Test, we recommend
viewing them before you continue with this final training.
After setting up an M-Y-E Test and submitting it to Amazon for Validation, you can check the status
of your experiment anytime on the M-Y-E home page.
An active status means that your experiment is in progress, and that customers viewing your listing
content are being split into two groups.
One group sees your original A content each time it appears in the Amazon store.
The other group sees your alternate B content.
You can usually review updated results for an experiment every one to two weeks by viewing its details
in M-Y-E.
If you decide to review results before an experiment ends, remember that they can fluctuate because
results represent actual customer behavior, including any atypical traffic over a short period of
time.
Results are more reliable when they're viewed after an experiment has run to significance, or if
it's run for at least eight to ten weeks.
We provide three types of M-Y-E results and present aggregate data if your test includes more than
one ASIN.
At the top of the results page, you'll see a percentage for the probability that one version of
your content is better than the other.
Underneath your probability percentage, you'll see a breakdown of metrics for your A and B content.
You can compare total units sold and total sales associated with the appearance of each version.
You can also view the sample size for each version of your content, which we use to calculate two
percentages.
The first is conversion rate, which is the number of customers who viewed a version of your detail
page content and made a purchase divided by the sample size.
The second percentage is units sold per unique visitor, which is the total units sold after customers
viewed a version of your content divided by the sample size.
The last result type you'll see for a completed M-Y-E test is the projected one-year impact of your
winning content.
We calculate this impact by determining the average daily units sold and the average daily sales
for both your losing and winning content.
We then subtract the losing averages from your winning ones and multiply by 365.
These estimates can't take seasonality, price changes, and other factors into account, so they aren't
a guarantee of future sales.
But they can help you understand how the results of your M-Y-E experiment might scale.
You'll see a most likely column for your projected one-year impact, which shows the average outcome
calculated.
You'll also see best-case and worst-case columns which show high and low outcomes calculated with
95% statistical confidence.
After reviewing the results of your experiment, you can publish your alternate content using standard
listing tools.
Or if you left the auto-publish option defaulted while setting up your M-Y-E test, we'll publish
your alternate content automatically, as long as it performed significantly better than your existing
listing content.
This concludes our training and our series on M-Y-E.
Thank you, and happy selling in the Amazon Store!